let savollar21 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "accustomed",
      answer: "C. odatlangan",
      options: [
        "A. begona",
        "B. charchagan",
        "C. odatlangan",
        "D. hayajonli"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "to affirm",
      answer: "A. tasdiqlamoq",
      options: [
        "A. tasdiqlamoq",
        "B. raqsga tushmoq",
        "C. pishirmoq",
        "D. uxlamoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "astonished",
      answer: "D. hayratda qolgan",
      options: [
        "A. charchagan",
        "B. och",
        "C. jahldor",
        "D. hayratda qolgan"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "to bang",
      answer: "B. dang'illatmoq",
      options: [
        "A. shivirlamoq",
        "B. dang'illatmoq",
        "C. suzmoq",
        "D. jilmaymoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "clan",
      answer: "C. qarindosh-urug'",
      options: [
        "A. bino",
        "B. transport",
        "C. qarindosh-urug'",
        "D. asbob"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "dim",
      answer: "A. xira",
      options: [
        "A. xira",
        "B. tez",
        "C. og'ir",
        "D. baland"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "emphasis",
      answer: "D. urg'u",
      options: [
        "A. rang",
        "B. ta'm",
        "C. hajm",
        "D. urg'u"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "fable",
      answer: "B. ertak",
      options: [
        "A. hisob",
        "B. ertak",
        "C. qurol",
        "D. chipta"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "feast",
      answer: "C. ziyofat",
      options: [
        "A. sport",
        "B. kasallik",
        "C. ziyofat",
        "D. transport"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "to glow",
      answer: "A. charaqlamoq",
      options: [
        "A. charaqlamoq",
        "B. yugurmoq",
        "C. yuvmoq",
        "D. ekmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "hollow",
      answer: "D. kavak",
      options: [
        "A. ho'l",
        "B. kuchli",
        "C. shirin",
        "D. kavak"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "instinct",
      answer: "B. tabiiy xulq",
      options: [
        "A. mebel",
        "B. tabiiy xulq",
        "C. mashina",
        "D. bino"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "joint",
      answer: "C. bo'g'im",
      options: [
        "A. ichimlik",
        "B. o'simlik",
        "C. bo'g'im",
        "D. kiyim"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "to leak",
      answer: "A. sizib chiqmoq",
      options: [
        "A. sizib chiqmoq",
        "B. kuylamoq",
        "C. chizmoq",
        "D. uchmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "physician",
      answer: "D. shifokor",
      options: [
        "A. novvoy",
        "B. rassom",
        "C. bog'bon",
        "D. shifokor"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "to sacrifice",
      answer: "B. qurbon qilmoq",
      options: [
        "A. o'ynamoq",
        "B. qurbon qilmoq",
        "C. sayohat qilmoq",
        "D. o'rganmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "stiff",
      answer: "C. egilmaydigan",
      options: [
        "A. yumshoq",
        "B. yengil",
        "C. egilmaydigan",
        "D. iliq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "to stroke",
      answer: "A. silamoq",
      options: [
        "A. silamoq",
        "B. sakramoq",
        "C. yopmoq",
        "D. hisoblamoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "tragic",
      answer: "D. fojiali",
      options: [
        "A. quvnoq",
        "B. shoshilinch",
        "C. kuchli",
        "D. fojiali"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "tune",
      answer: "B. kuy",
      options: [
        "A. kitob",
        "B. kuy",
        "C. stol",
        "D. deraza"
      ]
    }
];

export default savollar21;